poptent.net 2015-06-07

# Poptent : Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to you, the user ("You"), and to Poptent, Inc. ("Poptent"). Poptent will collect, use and disclose information that personally identifies You ("Personal Information") from its websites, [www.poptent.com](http://www.poptent.com/) and [www.poptent.net](http://www.poptent.net/) (collectively and together, the "Site") by the following principles. BY CONSENTING TO THE TERMS OF USE FOR THE SITE, OR BY ACCESSING THE SITE, YOU CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY (the "Policy"). If You do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

### Poptent COPPA Policy

Poptent is committed to complying fully with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”). Our information collection practices are described below. We urge all children to check with their parents before entering information on any website and we urge parents to discuss with their children restrictions regarding the online release of personal information to anyone they don’t know. This Site is a commercial website intended for people 18 years of age and older. Our email address and contact forms are not for use by those under the age of 13. In order to comply with COPPA we have elected to prohibit the use of our contact forms by pre-teens. By utilizing our contact forms You certify that You are at least 13 years of age or older.

Please do not email us or use the contact forms if You are under the age of 13 unless Your parents have first fully completed and signed the [Parental Notice and Consent Form](https://rightsignature.com/forms/Poptent-Parental--dba9f7/token/31c7e24eecd). By executing and uploading the Parental Notice and Consent Form, Your parents have, among other things, consented to allow Poptent to collect from, use and disclose Your Personal Information – Full Name, Age, Country, State, E-mail address, and, if applicable, other optional information, and have consented to Poptent’s use of “cookies” as described in Section 4 hereafter. Parental consent may be withdrawn at any time by contacting Poptent as provided in Section 4, in which case such Personal Information shall be deleted. If Poptent has not received a signed Parental Notice and Contact Form within a reasonable time after You have registered with the Site, Poptent will delete Your Personal Information within Your user account.

### 1\. Personal Information

The portion of the Site accessible to the general public will not expressly ask You for Personal Information or that allows the Site to contact You. The Site, however, will allow You to register and establish a profile containing information selected by You to showcase Yourself to Your peers and to the brand/agency personnel that will be visiting the Site to view advertisements created for their brands/clients ("Creator Profile"). You acknowledge and agree that any information that You place in a Creator Profile will be accessible by all users of the Site. Information contained in the Creator Profile is not considered Personal Information under this Agreement.

Portions of the Site will expressly ask You to register and generate a user ID ("Your Site Unique ID") and password ("Site Password") in order to access and use such portions. Certain other portions may require additional codes. The information that You provide to Poptent during the Poptent member registration or renewal process, including without limitation the information listed below, together with any additional information You provide to Poptent and information regarding the manner in which You use Your Poptent membership is considered Personal Information, will not be processed or disclosed by Poptent except as permitted by this Policy or as required or allowed by applicable law or legal process.

The following information is requested and/or collected when You register to become a member or update Your membership with the Site (collectively “Member Information”):

#### **Contact Information**

  * Full Name*
  * Date of Birth*
  * Home Address*
  * E-mail Address*
  * Telephone
  * Your Site Unique ID/Screen Name*
  * Site Password*
  * Short Biography
  * Portfolio Links

#### **Unique Identifiers**

* Required Information

The Site is not designed to attract children under 18 years old, and members are required to be 18 years of age or older or, if not 18 years of age, obtain parental consent. Accordingly, Poptent will not knowingly collect or maintain information at the Site from children.

### 2\. Accuracy of Personal Information

When possible, the Site will provide You with the means to make sure that Your Member Information is correct and current. You may view Your Member Information by entering the restricted portions of the Site using Your Site Unique ID and Site Password and certain other codes as necessary. To correct any factual inaccuracies, You must edit Your Member Information and press submit.

### 3\. Protection of Personal Information

Poptent endeavors to protect the security of Personal Information collected on the Site from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. The Site uses an encrypted connection when transferring Personal Information. Poptent also has put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to help safeguard and secure the information Poptent collects online in accordance with industry standards. When Poptent contracts with third parties to perform any services supporting the Site, Poptent requires that the third parties protect the security of the Personal Information collected with comparable security standards.

Neither passwords nor security systems are foolproof or necessarily work as intended, including encryption, and people can commit intentional crimes, make mistakes or fail to follow policies. Although Poptent takes what we believe are commercially reasonable security precautions, Poptent does not guaranty security. You agree to do what You reasonably can to help promote security (e.g., never reveal Your password or make it accessible to others).

If You or any other person believes they are a victim of identity theft entitled by law to request information from Poptent, contact Poptent as set forth in Section 4 below and provide all required information. Poptent will supply, without charge, the information legally required to be disclosed that Poptent then has, subject to applicable law and reserving all of our rights and defenses.

### 4\. Use of Personal Information & Opt-Out Policy

Poptent uses Your Personal Information: to operate the Site; to contact You (including without limitation regular email alerts); to affect, enforce, investigate, collect on and account for transactions related to the Site; to adjust Poptent's offerings of products and services; to provide information to sponsors; and to comply with applicable law. Poptent may provide Your Personal Information, or You may provide Your Personal Information directly, to sponsors and third parties who are responsible for implementing some of Poptent services (e.g., third party hosting). Unique identifiers are used to verify Your identity.

Poptent may aggregate Your Personal Information by combining it with information about other users or may remove characteristics of Your Personal Information, both of which make the Information non-personally identifiable. You grant us a royalty-free, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable and fully transferable right and license to use your Personal Information in connection with the creation and development of analytical and statistical analysis tools relating to the Site. Poptent is expressly authorized to make commercial use of data resulting therefrom, including without limitation, sharing such data with third parties, provided that we do not sell or otherwise transfer any part of the data that personally identifies any Site users.

Poptent uses Your Internet Protocol (IP) address to analyze trends, track a user's movement through the Site, help diagnose problems with Poptent's server, and to administer the Site. IP addresses are not linked to Personal Information, except to assist in debugging and validating the Site.

Members may opt-out of receiving future physical or electronic mailings, surveys or other information that is directly related to the operation of Poptent by changing settings within Your user account.

Poptent uses "cookies" to identify Your logged-in state through a Site Unique ID assigned to You during each login which is maintained until You log-out or delete Your cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on Your hard disk by a web server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to Your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to You and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to You.

The Site contains links to other sites, including to sponsors’ sites. Poptent is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites or of sponsors.

Poptent also uses outside companies to host portions of the Site and the advertisements. Poptent will require that these third parties do not further use or disclose Your Personal Information for any purpose other than providing the services.

Please be aware that this Policy and any choices You make on the Site will not necessarily apply to Personal Information You may have provided to Poptent in the context of other, separately operated, Poptent products or services.

Members may opt-out of receiving future physical or electronic mailings, surveys or other information that is not directly related to the operation of Poptent (such as membership renewal notices) by contacting Poptent using any of the following methods:

Email: info@poptent.com

Mail to the following postal address:

Webmaster  
Poptent, Inc.  
2401 Walnut Street, Suite 201  
Philadelphia, PA 19103

Call the following telephone number: (610) 832-1234  
Fax the following telephone number: (610) 397-0540

### 5\. Disclosure of Personal Information

The Site may store and disclose Personal Information as allowed or required by applicable law, including but not limited to making disclosures that are necessary or advisable to: (a) conform to legal or regulatory requirements or comply with legal process; and (b) protect the rights, safety or property of Poptent, the Site or others (including but not limited to other providers, sponsors, suppliers and vendors), or the users of the Site or the public.

### 6\. Public Forums

The Site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, and You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose Your Personal Information.

### 7\. Accountability

If at any time You believe that the Site has not adhered to the principles in this Policy, please notify Poptent as set forth in Section 4 above and Poptent will use good faith efforts to determine and correct the problem, if any.

### 8\. Freedom to Act

In addition to the above, Poptent may exercise all rights allowed by applicable law.

### 9\. Changes to this Policy

We reserve the right to change this Policy without prior notice. You can determine when this Policy was last revised by referring to the "last updated" date at the bottom of this Policy. Poptent encourages You to periodically review this Policy to stay informed about how we are helping to protect Personal Information Poptent collects. Your continued use of the Site constitutes Your consent to this Policy and any updates to it.

### 11\. Contacting the Site

Webmaster  
Poptent, Inc.  
2401 Walnut Street, Suite 201  
Philadelphia, PA 19103  
Email: info@poptent.com  
Phone: 610-832-1234  
Fax: 610-397-0540

Last Updated 4/16/2014
